bleachworld.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy // Viz

## VIZ Media Privacy Policy

Effective Date September 24, 2007 (last updated October 25, 2016)

* * *

**About this Policy**

| 

This policy describes our privacy practices for our websites, mobile websites, smart phone applications and programming services (the "Sites").  
  
---|---  
  
**Information We Collect**

| 

**Contact information** : For example, we might collect your name and street address. We might also collect your phone number or email.

**Payment information** : If you make purchases or subscribe to services, we might collect your credit card information.

**Demographic information** : We may collect information about products you like, services you use or what you buy. We might also ask for information like your age.

**Third Party Information** : We might collect a friend's email address to send them an electronic postcard. We may also collect contact information to get a parent's consent if a minor wants to use our site.

**Other Information** : If you use our Sites, we may collect information about the browser or platform you are using. We might track the pages you visit. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. We collect this information using the tracking tools described below.  
  
**How We Collect Information**

| 

**We collect information directly from you.** The following are a few examples of when we collect information from you:

  * If you register on our Sites.
  * If you register for a promotion.
  * If you register for one of our programs.
  * If you make purchases on our sites.
  * If you subscribe to programming services.
  * If you leave comments on our sites.
  * If you make contact requests.

**We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. To learn more about these tools click described below.

**Some of our Sites and applications use analytics software, including Display Advertising.** You can opt-out of analytics software and personalized ads/recommendations from Flurry by clicking [here](https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do "https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do"). You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by using the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCiXfE-h214dkoG5felTGgYsZ1rbdfjsTz6U4tuYCSNMpkhsRHSBA1XfvGQdoBElG9XSAZNLXbTWaCW7RllbEl-nQVHMKgu49nqrIB9yYrawQ1LxA6qldP_VeeH06P5lzodVg9TZzZt0Ww0UKZqQvqwuJN5oyY3-5yw2noQSFB_vN8Azbg65-lfSdnlEKXmk6YWWO6Tv). You may also want to implement the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-analytics-opt-out/fllaojicojecljbmefodhfapmkghcbnh?hl=en).  
  
**How We Use Information**

| 

We use your information as is disclosed at the time we collect the information and in the following ways:

**To respond to your requests or questions.** Examples include:

  * Fulfilling subscription requests or prizes.
  * Registering you for promotions or our Sites.

**To improve our products and services.** We might use your information to customize your experience with us.

**To look at site trends and customer interests.** We may use your information to make website or product improvements. We may also combine information we get from you with information about you we have gotten from third parties.

**For security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our Sites.

**To promote us and our various Sites.** Unless we tell you otherwise, we might send you notices of special promotions, offers or solicitations. We might tell you about new Site features or product or service offerings. To manage this, follow the instructions in Your Choices, below.

**To communicate with you about your account or our relationship.** We may contact you to tell you about changes to this Policy or our Terms. We may also tell you about issues with your orders.

**To talk to parents or guardians to get permission.** We may use contact information to get permission from parents for children who want to use our site.  
  
**Information Sharing**

|  | 

**We may share your information as follows:**

| 

**Can you limit?**  
  
---|---  
  
**Within our company.**

| 

No  
  
**If we think we have to in order to comply with the law.** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests.

| 

No  
  
**With any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold we may sell our customer list as part of that transaction.

| 

No  
  
**With third parties who perform services on our behalf.** For example, we share information with vendors, or will authorize them to collect information on our behalf. Some vendors may be located outside of the United States.

| 

No  
  
**With our business partners.** For example, we might share information with a business partner who is running a joint promotion with us. We might also share information to trusted business partners whose products we think you would like. To opt out of having your information shared, see the Your Choices section below.

| 

In some circumstances  
  
**Your Choices**

| 

To stop receiving our promotional emails, [email us](mailto:optout@viz.com) opt-out request. When logged in to certain of our Sites, registered users can also change their options at the Your Account page.

To opt out of having us share your information with third parties for their promotional purposes, please [email us](mailto:optout@viz.com). If you accept an offer from one of them after you opt out, we will share your information with that specific party.

You can choose whether or not to share personal information. If you choose not to share, some parts of our sites and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use. If you turn off cookies or tracking tools, parts of our site and services may also not work properly.  
  
**More Questions?**

| 

You can [email us](mailto:privacypolicy@viz.com) or write to us at:

Online Manager (Privacy Issue) VIZ Media   
1355 Market Street, Suite #200   
San Francisco, CA 94103   
(415) 546-7073  
  
**Our Sites and Children**

| 

The sites on which this policy appears are not intended for children under 13. We take steps on these sites to avoid collecting information online from children under 13. In some cases, children may give us information without us knowing about it. If you are a parent or legal guardian and believe that your child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, please [email us](mailto:privacypolicy@viz.com). If you want to write, use the address listed above. Please mark your inquiries to the attention of "COPPA - Information Request" and include your email and phone number.

Learn more about how to protect your child online. Read the [helpful information provided by the FTC](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/features/feature-0002-parents).   
  
**Security**

| 

We use industry standard means to protect our Sites and your information. The Internet is not 100% secure, though. We thus cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet.

Online access to your personal information is protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not share your password.  
  
**Links**

| 

Our sites contain links to third party sites. If you click on one of those links, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the information practices of that website. You should read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for such third party's sites.  
  
**California Privacy Rights**

| 

If you live in California and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a list of the personal information we have shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. We will also give you a list of the third parties that have received your information. You can make a request one time each year.

To exercise your rights, you can [email us ](mailto:privacypolicy@viz.com)or write to us at the address in the "More Questions" section, above. Mention in your letter that you are making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. We will respond within 30 days.  
  
**Updating Personal Information**

| 

On certain of our Sites, if you are registered user, you may be able to do the following with your personal information:

  * Review it
  * Correct it
  * Update it
  * Delete/deactivate it

Log on to our Site and click on "My Account" to make changes.  
  
**Policy Updates**

| 

This Policy was updated on September 24, 2012. Where allowed by law, changes to our policy will be applied to information we already have.  
  
## VIZ Media and Our Tracking Tools

* * *

**Tracking Technologies We Use**

| 

We or our vendors use several common tracking tools. These may include browser cookies. We may also use web beacons and similar technologies. We use these tools to track our consumers and Site visitors. We also use them for other business purposes, including:

  * To track new visitors to our sites.
  * To recognize past customers.
  * To store your password if you are registered on our sites.
  * To serve you with advertising content in which we think you will be interested. As part of this customization, we may observe your behaviors on this Site or on other websites. We may also get information about your browsing history from our trusted business partners.
  * So we can better understand our audience, our customers, our Site visitors, and their respective interests.

---|---  
  
**Controlling Our Use of Tracking Technologies**

| 

You may control our use of cookies. How you do so depends on the type of cookie. You can set your browser to reject browser cookies. To control flash cookies, which we may use on certain Sites from time to time, you can go [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). Why? Because flash cookies cannot be controlled through your browser settings.

NOTE: If you set your computer to block cookies, you may not be able to use certain features on our sites.

We work with Twitter to bring you more useful and interesting advertising content. You may find instructions on how to opt out of Twitter's collection of remarketing data [here](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405).  
  
**About Our Ads on Other Websites**

| 

We may also work with online advertising companies to provide you with advertising that is as relevant and useful as possible. We may provide this advertising on our Sites and other third party sites that you visit. These ads may be based on information you submit on our Sites or third party sites. They may also be based on your activities or behaviors on our Sites or on third party sites. The information gathered may be used to serve you with advertisements on our Sites or on third party websites. This includes mobile websites or applications.  
  
**Opting Out of Receiving/Seeing Tracking-Based Ads**

| 

We sometimes work with vendors to provide you with online ads. What ads you see may be based on your activities on our Site or third party sites. To opt out of having your online behavior tracked for advertising purposes click [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
